Hey-hey, l'chaim!
Shit.
Exc-Excuse me.
What you did up there
was very impressive.
Oh, thanks, man.
How do you do it?
- Do... what?
- Well, you-you know, the...
You know? All of it.
Oh, you mean rap?
No, all of it.
The way you look, talk,
your demeanor,
your facial expressions
where, you know,
people think it's real.
Man, I don't know what the hell
you're talking about, man.
Could...
- could you teach my son?
- Man, teach your son what, man?
You know, just to...
how to be like you.
- Teach him how to rap.
I want to hire you.
He makes more videos than songs,
I don't understand it.
Man, it ain't that easy,
big dawg, all right?
Well, I just want to--
maybe he could shadow you,
absorb for a week.
Maybe you could take a couple
of selfies, give him some tips.
Hey, look, man,
I'm kind of busy, all right?
So, like, why don't you
reach out to my manager?
But I'm telling you, I don't
think I got the time, man.
I'll pay you a million dollars.
Hey, hey ♪
- Fuck.
-* Money good ♪
Throw up where I'm from ♪
Let 'em know I'm still hood ♪
♪ I ain't had to get
nobody hit ♪
But I could ♪
♪ Before I post a pic,
should I flex? ♪
Yeah, I should ♪
♪ I ain't gotta worry
'bout shit ♪
-* Money good *
-* Ah. ♪
All right, all right.
We just signed a new recruit.
So I'm gonna need all hands
on deck for this one.
Cathy, can you pull the video up
on the big screen, please?
Back off. Stop right there.
Do you have anything on you?
Okay, no, no, no, get down...
Lauren Loughty.
She's one of ours.
This is her.
Her book is climbing exponentially
on The New York Times
Best Sellers list.
Oh, wow.
I just finished that book.
It gave me a real paradigm shift
on how things may not always be
as they seem.
Well, so now the kid
in the video is suing her,
which is causing a dip in sales.
We have a few companies interested
in securing the rights,
so we need this to go away.
And fast.
Let's talk ideas,
new image, rebranding.
Hit me.
MANAGER 1:
Maybe we show the kid
has a checkered past.
MANAGER 2:
Or we can put out crime data
from that neighborhood
to show she was in the right
trying to defend herself.
MANAGER 3:
Oh, what if we had her donate
to the kid's football team?
I mean, it's tax deductible.
:
Can we just work
on our other signees?
What did he just say?
Uh, I was asking,
can we work on other signees?
Everybody is already assigned.
Lauren Loughty is
the priority right now.
Can we sign new people?
Our hands are full right now,
unless you can wrangle
a prestige act--
your D'Angelos, Banksys.
I could probably get D'Angelo.
Have at it.
:
Great.
Moving on...
Cathy, what's next
on the agenda?
Hey, what's up?
What's up?
Can I help you?
Yeah, man.
I'm... I'm Paper Boi.
The rapper.
Song's dead. What's next?
Uh, yo, can you put on that
"Do the Ricky Rock"?
Uh... sure.
- Cool.
- What's the Ricky Rock?
Fuck if I know, bro.
That's for the Internet
to decide.
Yo, I'm supposed to be working
with somebody named Benny.
One of y'all Benny?
- Who?
- Yeah, that's me.
Great. Hey, man.
I'm Paper Boi.
The rapper.
Paper Boi, you know?
Oh, you the dude my dad bought.
Yeah, tight, tight, tight.
All right.
Uh, this Yodel Kid.
We just vibin', bro.
Yo.
I know you.
I used to listen to you
when I was a kid.
- That's what's up.
That's great, wonderful.
Uh, what you need
help with, man? Can you...?
Oh, no, we cool.
My dad's just extra.
He want to help out and shit,
but you can just chill
and collect that check.
I'm about to get in the booth.
- It's time, you know?
- Yep.
Yeah, this shit's gonna be fire.
Hell yeah, it is.
We gonna change the game
with this shit, bro.
Look at this shit.
Hey! Lil Rick Moranis.
What's kosh'?
You ready to kill
this shit, bro?
- I was born to kill.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- What's up, man?
- What's up, baby?
- Hey, you know Yodel Kid?
- Oh, what's up, man?
- Lil Rick Moranis.
You know, Honey I Shrunk
the Kids looking ass.
- What's going on, man?
- Paper Boi, dawg.
Shit, I know who you are, sir.
- Oh.
- Bunk.
I'm with Lil Rick.
Yeah, man, I know who you are.
I like your music, dawg.
- Ah, that's what's up.
- Mm.
-* I'm Rickin' *
- Hey.
I'm rockin' ♪
I'm tickin' ♪
So, you want to hang out
with these little kids...
I'm tockin' ♪
...or you want to converse
in Studio Three?
-* I'm Rickin' *
- Yo.
- Say less, man.
-* I'm rockin' ♪
Studio Three it is.
This shit slaps, bro,
I told you.
Oh, yeah, man.
What's up?
- Man, all right, hmm, fuck that
Rickin' and rockin',
tickin' and tockin'.
"I'm Rick..."
Man, get the fuck on, right?
It's almost like
it's not even rap, you know?
I know what you gonna say.
You gonna say that the game
is fucked and yada yada yada,
whoopty-whoop, but, like...
I don't know, man.
Mm.
Just go collect my million,
dip the fuck out.
You making a million off this?
Crazy, right?
You should be making ten.
Yeah, but...
I'm just banking this money,
though, man.
Saving it up,
investing and shit.
Hey, I stay on
that Robinhood app.
That ain't making money.
I mean, stocks and bonds,
I mean, that's cool
if you want to be a dentist
living in Castlewood,
driving a Tesla with your wife.
But you and I both know
this lifestyle ain't cheap.
Saving money ain't making money.
And you're letting
the real money pass by.
Yeah, but other than touring,
that's the only way
to make money
in this music business, man.
- Mm-mm.
- Oh.
You know, me and a couple of
my guys, we be getting together,
we be talking about this
every once in a while.
We're actually getting together
tomorrow night.
You should come through.
Rally's?
In Georgia?
Hey, um...
I'm here to see D'Angelo?
Thank you.
Come on in.
We're just getting started.
- Glad to see you.
- Yeah, what's up?
What's going on?
Sit here?
Hey, what's up, man?
Psst. Psst.
Thanks.
All right, y'all,
listen up, man.
I'm only gonna say this
one time.
If you in here,
it means you care
about your future.
But this is not about rap.
If you in here dealing in rap,
then you can leave right now.
Everybody in here
can rap they asses off.
But if rapping
meant you made money,
then Cassidy would be
a fucking billionaire.
Take a look at this slide.
Now, can you guess
which one of these people
is a Billboard charting
rap artist
with billions
of streams globally?
It's simple.
We all know that optics
is everything.
With my system...
...I'm tossing your
Black ass a life raft.
I can help my brother better
- when I'm at the top.
- Mm-hmm.
Now...
Look at this.
Memorize this.
Go to sleep dreaming about this.
What's a YWA, man?
Wait.
Young...
white...
avatar.
One of them kids
that you was hanging out
in the studio with yesterday.
GAS 90:
See, you-you-you got
to get one
and-and-and train him
and nurture him and...
try to catch 'em all.
Nigga, Pokémon?
Exactly.
Man, look,
I can make an album
better than them kids,
win a Grammy, and then use
the clout to go on tour again.
- Mm.
- And your album
will be better,
but nobody wants to hear you.
'Cause you old.
You can never get bigger
than your last album.
Y'all niggas trippin'.
- GAS 90: We trippin'?
- Yeah.
Bunk, show him the slide.
See, there's three stages
to this thing.
The first one is Young Street.
That was all of us
when we first started out.
All swagger.
Then, it's OG.
See, the young kids,
they look up to us,
they respect the influence.
Finally, it's Family Films.
Now, see, right here,
you're right on the cusp of OG.
But you?
You think you got
all the time in the world,
but in actuality you gonna be
Ice Cube's best friend
in Are We There Yet? 5
in less than a year.
That's bullshit, man.
That's bullshit.
I'm still hot out here, man.
I just did an arena tour.
And what's bigger than an arena?
You think you're selling out
soccer stadiums, my nigga?
All that goes up must go down.
Let me ask you a question.
When you was in the studio
yesterday with those kids,
- they even know who you were?
Man, fuck them kids.
- Man, look.
Niggas still checking for me
'cause I speak for the streets.
You heard me?
Man, the streets can't feed you.
What, you want to end up
like Blueblood?
I loved that nigga,
and I didn't even know
he had an album out
till he was in the ground
for five months.
You could downsize
your whole lifestyle
and be fine.
Live out in the country
in the middle of nowhere.
But if you want this lifestyle,
you better get a YWA
in the next five months...
...while they still
remember you.
Ladies, hands up, ladies.
Okay, fellas, hands up.
Yo, I used to go
to this school, yep.
Yo, check it, uh...
I'm old-school like 2005 ♪
If you're older than that ♪
♪ Then you're probably
'bout to die ♪
♪ My teacher used to tell me
I won't be shit ♪
♪ But I just made a million
livestreaming on Twitch. ♪
Yo, yo, yo!
Go "Livestreaming."
Livestreaming.
Right now, phones out,
phones out, check it.
Y'all want some money?
Who wants that cash money?
Oh, shit.
We got some fine-ass honeys
over here.
You want some money?
Here you go, hey.
I'll be goddamned.
Okay, that's for you.
I swear, what's your Instagram?
I swear I've seen you somewhere...
You need to get
off the premises.
It's okay, man.
You want some percs?
No congregating,
no congregating...
- Anyway...
- Hey.
Hey, you remember me?
I'm Paper Boi.
- Oh, what's up, man?
- Hey, what's going...?
How you doing, my man?
- It's been so long.
- Can you get Benny for me?
- Mm-hmm.
- You remember who Benny is?
- Mm-mm.
All right, man.
Let me back you up a little bit.
Okay.
- Oh!
- Oh, shit. You good?
- You good? Can you...?
- I'm fine. I'm-I'm...
I'm fucking amazing, man.
I'm good, buddy.
- Hey, Benny.
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
- Who want a pic, huh?
- Hey.
- Who want a pic? You want a pic?
- Hey, Benny.
- Yeah, DM me. DM me.
- Oh, shit.
What's up, Paper Boi?
- Come on, man.
- Let me talk to you real quick.
- How you doing, bro?
- Yeah, what's up?
- Hey, look.
Whatever you think you got
going on here, man,
I think... that me and you
should, you know,
solidify our relationship
a little bit.
'Cause, I mean, you got
real potential, man,
and I... I just think
we need to streamline it
- a little bit more.
- Yeah, I feel you, yeah.
All right, great.
Yeah, great, great, man.
Look, with me as your manager,
I can make sure you get
all the things you need
to be the star
you want to be, man.
- Oh, shit, management?
- Yeah.
Damn, bro.
I'm sorry, but I just
signed with Bunk.
- What?
- Yeah, bro.
- Bunk?
- Yeah, Bunk.
He talked to me that day
we were all at the studio.
Bro, like, pulled me to the
side, he laid it all out.
- He's a good guy.
- Yep.
- Yeah.
You should talk to him
sometime, bro, he's good.
That's... Yeah, man, yep.
- Yeah.
- Yep.
Anyway, we got to--
yeah, we got to roll
'cause I got, like, two more
high schools to hit up.
- Okay. Huh.
-: I can't believe
we're getting away
with this shit, bro.
- Right.
- This shit is crazy. I'm rich.
- I'm number one, bro.
- Okay.
I'm number one!
Send me a pic!
Hey, hey, Benny, hold up.
- Fuck, man
- Wait.
Shit, that girl was hot.
Holy shit.
Hey, hang on, Benny, I'm coming.
Hold up.
- Yo, thanks for giving me
a ride, man.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
Mm.
Hold up, man,
before you get in my car,
you gonna be all right?
Shit, man.
I'm a fucking legend.
I'm gonna live forever, baby.
You're gonna get
a legendary ass-beating,
- you vomit on my paint, boy.
- Vomit away from the car, man.
Hey, man.
Y'all got any water?
Mm-mm.
No.
No. Unacceptable.
Unacceptable.
All right?
I want to see D'Angelo, okay?
I've been here all fucking week.
All right?
Where's D'Angelo?
Can I please see D'Angelo?
What is D'Angelo?
We are D'Angelo.
Let me experience...
D'Angelo.
When living for my life ♪
Was everything ♪
A man could want... ♪
I could never see ♪
:
* See tomorrow ♪
I was never told ♪
About the ♪
About that sorrow ♪
And ♪
How can you mend ♪
A broken heart? ♪
How can you stop the rain ♪
From falling down? ♪
Tell me, how can you stop ♪
Yeah, oh... ♪
The sun from shining? ♪
♪ What makes the world
go 'round? ♪
And ♪
How can you mend... ♪
Speak.
You're not D'Angelo.
You asked to experience
D'Angelo.
In this moment, for you,
we are D'Angelo.
I haven't bathed in four days.
Hmm.
I thought this was some
"D'Angelo needs a manager
with patience" type shit.
I need to sign D'Angelo.
These people
are not true believers
and unworthy
of D'Angelo's presence.
Would you like to know
what a D'Angelo is?
♪ That rustles
through the trees ♪
Sure. Sure.
♪ And misty memories
of days gone by ♪
A D'Angelo is a complex network
of men, women and D'Angelos
spread across countries,
Earth and light.
You have proven yourself
worthy of our visage.
So now you are a protector.
* La, la, la, la, la. ♪
How can you mend ♪
A broken heart... ♪
If I don't go back
with the real D'Angelo,
I'm...
I'm in a little bit of trouble.
Hmm.
Yes. Yes, yes.
Since you were eight,
you always had a dream
where you were swimming,
and below are hands
grasping to reach you.
You struggle to keep them
from pulling you under.
You fight to stay free.
Why are you so certain
the hands intend to harm you?
-* Help me *
-* Help me ♪
Help me mend my heart ♪
Thank you.
My broken heart ♪
I just wanna... ♪
Protector...
...this...
:
...whole operation
is rather expensive.
Did you...
did you really want to sign me?
Yeah, but... no, I can't.
Sorry.
Somebody tell me ♪
You sound good though.
Thank you.
:
I sound...
I sound good.
That's all right.
Help me mend my... ♪
Here we go, here we go.
- Pose.
- Mm. Grammys, bro.
Beat time, baby.
Boogie Bunk.
What's happening, baby?
- Just living the dream?
- Yes, sir.
Yo, I'm gonna check out the bar
real quick.
All right.
Make it a single.
- What's up, man?
Man, I told you.
These kids can take us places
we haven't been before.
- Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
- Hey, yo, yo.
- What's going on?
- Paper Boi.
- Haven't seen you in a minute.
- Yeah.
- What's going on?
Oh, man, you know.
Coolin' it. Coolin' it
- like I do.
- Mm-hmm.
That's what's up.
Listen, I want
to apologize about Benny.
Part of the game.
I hope you weren't offended.
Hey, man, no.
No offense taken.
No. No, I learned a lot
from y'all, man.
- Good.
- Yeah.
You see what I've been
telling you?
You see where these kids got us?
I mean, we're at
the Grammy's, baby.
- Yeah.
- What's up?
So, Paper Boi,
what you nominated for?
Oh, man, I'm--
I'm not nominated.
Yeah, I'm just here
supporting my new artist.
- New artist?
- Mm-hmm.
Al, you found one?
- Hmm.
- Good for you.
Yeah, man, yeah, yeah.
You might've heard of Yodel Kid?
- I'm sorry, that was you?
- Yeah, man.
Platinum in three weeks.
I mean, it's crazy
how fast things travel
on streaming nowadays, no?
GAS 90:
That record been out what?
11 fucking days, man?
11 fucking days, man.
GAS 90:
You had to pay somebody.
Don't we all?
Ah, you don't, though.
I mean...
We gonna catch you inside.
Yeah, you will.
Yes, you will.
:
Yes, they get paid.
What's going on, bruh?
Hey, Benny.
Hey, what's up, Paper Boi?
- What's going on?
- Yeah, what's going on?
Hey, hey. You heard
from Yodel Kid, man?
'Cause I've been callin'
his ass all day.
- You know where he at?
- Oh, yeah.
Uh...
He's dead.
He dead-- What?
Yeah, the driver went
to pick him up
a couple of hours ago,
and they found him.
Probably, like,
OD'd like crazy, bro.
It's all over my feed
right now, it's goin'...
Man, let me see this shit.
Talkin' about...
-"Lost a legend." "RIP."
- Yeah.
What the...
He died, man?
Yeah.
You're probably gonna win
that Grammy.
Bet.
And the winner is--
and this was a no-brainer--
Yodel Kid, "Born to Die."
I just want to say
thank you to everyone
who was playing his music
on the streets today.
You know, he always said
all he wanted to be
was a legend and, wow,
he really did it.
- Huh, that was weird.
I'm telling you,
Grammys ain't for a Black man.
Mm.
Congrats.
Hmm.
Man, I don't know,
I don't know if I'm cut out
for the managing part,
you know what I'm saying?
It just made me feel...
sick?
Yeah.
How you do it, man?
Um...
I just remember it's not about
what feels good.
It's about...
what survives.
Yeah. Um...
Yeah, I got a meeting
on the westside
in the morning, so...
This is on me.
I'll see y'all.
- Easy.
- I'll see y'all later, hmm?
- Always working.
- Yeah.
All right, man.
Actually, uh...
a guy, Mickey Boston,
he's got this after-party.
You comin'?
All good, man. I'm good.
- All right. Wham.
- Bam.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- You know it.
-* Yeah *
-* Out of sight ♪
♪ You're out of mind,
you're out of luck ♪
♪ It's like nobody even care
if you be 'round ♪
♪ Why I fall off with my niggas
when I'm up? ♪
♪ Why nobody stand up for me
when I'm down? ♪
♪ You back in jail and this time
they say you stuck ♪
♪ Everybody laughin' at you
like a clown ♪
♪ Why the only time you hate me
when I'm up? ♪
♪ And why the only time
you love me when I'm down? ♪
♪ Why I lost best new artist
to Khalid, 2017? ♪
♪ We all knew
that should've been me ♪
♪ But I never hated,
I congratulated ♪
♪ Shit, at least
I was nominated ♪
♪ But if Cardi B win,
then I won, too ♪
♪ I do it for the real niggas
'cause I'm one, too ♪
♪ The fact I made it
out the shit ♪
That they be goin' through ♪
♪ Will make 'em feel
like if I win ♪
Then they won, too ♪
Lil' buddy got popped ♪
♪ Some niggas
in the squad, too ♪
♪ And why them niggas
turned around ♪
And say they know it's you? ♪
Keep it real ♪
♪ Why the hell
I wanna harm you? ♪
When everything I drop ♪
♪ They said they
wanted part two ♪
I heard his Benz got dropped ♪
And they went and point you. ♪
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org